TYPHOON FAMILY
TYPHOON TRADING
CEO KANG TAE-POONG
You're the CEO now.
Yes.
I just became
the CEO now.
But I have no employees…
or any money…
or any things to sell.
But what I'm trying to say is,
Ms. Oh Mi-seon…
Will you come and work…
for Typhoon Trading…
as a trader?
Yes.
I will.
ULCHI 4-GA TO ANYANG STATION
-Sir.
-Goodness.
-Hello, sir.
-Hey.
I came to pick up my cards.
-Typhoon Trading?
-Yes, that's right.
-Here it is.
-Thank you.
-It's 5,000 won.
-It's 5,000 won?
-Thank you for the business.
-Thank you.
-The pink one?
-Yes.
TYPHOON TRADING
-You're here.
-Hey.
-You got here early.
-Yes.
Have a cup of coffee.
-Careful.
-Thank you.
Oh, right.
A present for you.
-For me?
-Yes.
TYPHOON TRADING
SENIOR STAFF OH MI-SEON
Let's have a good run, Ms. Senior Staff.
Thank you,
Mr. CEO.
CEO?
-You're the CEO now.
-Yes, you're right.
Thank you for the coffee.
THE FALL OF THE NATIONAL FINANCE INSTITUTE
PARK SEONG-GEUN
YUSEONG TRADING
Gosh, Typhoon Trading.
So, where are you dumping these?
My dad hates leaving things here
for a prolonged period.
When can we make money off these?
I'm looking into it,
but there are two containers of these.
It's a huge supply,
and the fabric is high quality,
so it's hard to handle.
I'm considering
selling these to a company in China.
Hey, before you send these to China,
let's leave Tae-poong some
so he can make a pair of pants.
He must've wet them.
You're laughing even harder than me.
PYO MERCHANT MARINE
Do you have a habit
of coming over unannounced?
TYPHOON TRADING
These are the fax records
we exchanged with the Italian company
when we imported the fabric.
They'll accept the return
after taking 30% of the fee,
so please send them there.
Although it's 30%,
we'll get more in return
with this kind of exchange rate.
Why are you telling me this?
Because it was a promise,
a promise our company made.
So you'd rather lose money
than your credibility?
What if I refuse?
Well, you can do that too,
if you can sell those
at a higher price than the original.
Why don't you
just hand over the company to me?
Then I'll give you enough money to get by.
You said my company was worthless,
so it's a surprise you want to buy it.
There must be something important
at Typhoon Trading.
There's nothing more important
than money to a businessman.
You know,
even if I agree to take the deal,
you'd be better off
staying out of the business.
People never change.
You will fail again,
just as you did this time.
Mr. Pyo.
You should teach
those baby steps to Hyun-jun instead.
I am currently
learning how to fly
from my father.
I will fall
and fall
over and over again.
Then one day,
I will soar
high over your head, Mr. Pyo.
Hand over the company?
How ridiculous.
-This is Typhoon--
-Hey!
Why won't you people
ever pick up the phone?
I just did.
Hey, Kang Tae-poong.
You have no idea
your fabric is gone, do you?
-Sorry? What fabric?
-These.
Wait, why are these…
-Did you import these?
-What?
-How do you have the exact same batch?
-Good grief.
Didn't you say this was worth
26 years of your dad's life?
Doesn't this ring a bell?
No?
Last time,
you held onto all this fabric
and made a huge scene.
-Yes.
-So when you had to unload these,
the parking lot was too tiny,
and you said you were broke.
These are crooked,
and you can't let them go over.
It'll cost more if it does.
You have to make sure these are intact.
You can always pay for more.
-I don't have money.
-Really?
Did it go over?
It looked like
you had no more space to unload these,
and I knew it'd be tough for you two
if I unloaded them and left.
So, I thought
I'd keep these in my truck for a while.
But gosh,
why didn't you pick up my calls?
Gosh, what are we going to do?
I kept paging Go Ma-jin,
but he never called me back.
And I finally got in contact with you.
I'm sorry.
A lot has happened.
Do you know how much I lost
while hauling these around
instead of loading stuff for my job?
Are you going to pay me for my labor?
-I will.
-With what? You lost everything.
I didn't.
I didn't lose everything. I got these.
Just these?
The word already got around
about how you got duped by Mr. Pyo.
No.
I can sell these, Mr. Baek.
I'll sell all of these!
-Are you serious?
-I'm dead serious!
All right. Go ahead and do that then.
How many rolls do I have?
I knew a few were missing.
I knew it.
I felt like
I didn't unload everything back then.
There will be no logistics cost,
so let's just return these.
Where are the files?
Tae-poong is too overwhelmed
to notice that these are gone.
It's the shipping contract.
SHIPPING CHARTER CONTRACT
The quantity says 50,000.
Take a look. It's 50,000 yds.
The quantity must exactly be the same.
Do you know
how hard it was for me
to pocket this out of the office?
It was a tough job.
RELEASOR: TYPHOON TRADING
SUCCESSOR: PYO MERCHANT MARINE
This is yours.
Don't give me this out here.
I deserve this.
We have it by color.
Two, four, six, eight, ten.
It sounds about right.
Off to Italy! Close it!
Lower the container!
3 DAYS AGO
There it is. It's the refund policy.
It's possible if there is no change
in quantity or quality.
How many rolls did you say
there were in Mr. Baek's truck?
There were 100 rolls, so it's 5,000 m.
But if Pyo Merchant Marine finds out that
10% went missing…
Then, Pyo Merchant Marine
wouldn't send it for a refund.
That's why
I took a closer look and realized…
Where is it?
Look at the quantity.
It's missing the unit.
So what if I make it seem like…
You know, that thing.
How about we
make them think it's in yards?
-Yards?
-Yes, so it'd be 50,000 yds, not 50,000 m.
Then 50,000 yds would be 45,000 m,
exactly what Pyo has now.
I think they'll return it
if the quantity matches.
That'd be the most helpful.
Who's going to tell them that?
It'll be suspicious if you do it randomly.
Well, someone who wishes
Typhoon Trading would go down
or someone who resents me.
Or…
You two were here.
You haven't shut the place down?
Why do I care?
Mr. Kang Tae-poong.
What's this? Why did you send me this?
SAVINGS ACCOUNT, GO MA-JIN
Are you trying
to make me feel uncomfortable?
I do not feel uncomfortable at all.
Not only couldn't I care less
about this business,
but above all, I find you,
Mr. Kang Tae-poong,
just awful.
-We found him.
-We did.
What?
He's gone.
Take this.
You earned this.
So what? Do you expect me to keep it?
That's called fraud, people.
No matter how much I think about it,
I don't look anything like a traitor,
so why did it have to be me?
Why did I go to the office
and get entangled in this?
Just take it.
-Please take this.
-No.
I told you already. I don't want it.
This was left for you by my father,
and it's your severance pay and salary.
SAVINGS ACCOUNT, GO MA-JIN
That's supposed to come to me
from the company fund.
But this was
out of Mr. Kang's pocket.
It feels so wrong. No.
I can't stand something like this.
Okay. We're done here.
The two of you should
keep it reasonable.
I'm glad I got a chance
to mess with Mr. Ha, though.
But if anything draws out for too long,
it becomes ugly. I'm leaving.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Take care.
Goodbye.
We just have to wait now.
Yes.
Italy will realize it right away
as soon as they open it.
They're missing 10% of the rolls.
They might even get mad,
thinking they got tricked.
So,
do you think Mr. Pyo will make the deal?
We'll have to see
if he's a businessman
who's more concerned about immediate gains
or if causes are more important to him.
What are you talking about?
We didn't get the refund?
Italy reached out
and said the quantity is different.
The quantity?
-Didn't we send everything?
-We did.
But it's different from the quantity
written on the contract
sent from Italy as evidence.
Hey, Mr. Ha.
You're so good at doing your job.
I checked the quantity,
but there was a mix-up with the unit.
The units were different.
The contract specifies 50,000 m,
not 50,000 yds.
So I calculated the difference
between the two,
and 50,000 yds in meters…
The quantity we sent was 45,720 m,
which leaves out 5,000 m.
And?
If we do not immediately return
all 50,000 m,
they will ship everything back to us.
Ship everything back?
A second return? That's insane.
And then?
And then, sir?
Yes, sir.
And then,
we must pay the shipping fees and
logistics fees regarding this contract,
and we'll have to find
another client as soon as possible.
Empty your mind
and come up with a better idea.
-Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
Mr. Pyo.
Mr. Kang Tae-poong,
the CEO of Typhoon Trading, has called.
Kang Tae-poong?
The CEO?
You devised an interesting scheme.
You should've called
if you were in need of help.
Hyun-jun and I aren't total strangers.
What are you trying to say?
It's the remaining 10% of the fabric.
The cost price is 11,240,000 won,
and one separate condition
is that you must pay up front in cash.
SALES AGREEMENT
Did you say 11,240,000 won?
No.
That's our cost price.
The asking price is…
Twice as much?
You two both have lost your minds.
Then let's triple it.
It'll be 33,720,000 won.
Do you really think I'll buy this?
Wouldn't it be better
if you sent the rest to get the refund
than to pay the logistics fee as a penalty
and end up with the stock?
That sounds much better.
Otherwise,
you can lose money and keep your pride.
That's cool too.
Stop talking bullshit and get lost.
How dare you try to pull this on us?
Get Mr. Ha here.
-Yes, sir.
-Dad, you're going to buy this?
Let's just go.
It doesn't cost much anyway.
I need to make at least another penny.
That's what's important now.
Why are you doing this?
Let's destroy this punk.
Hey.
Did you just laugh?
Is this funny to you?!
Why did you laugh?
-Do you feel like you won?
-No.
It's amusing.
Is that so?
Have your laugh.
-Wait, Dad.
-Move.
-Ms. Oh.
-Yes?
It's fun.
To be a trader.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
We have to go.
SAPDARI LOGISTICS
EPISODE 4
THE WIND CANNOT STOP ME
Hey.
Look who it is.
Hello, sir.
WAREHOUSE FLOOR PLAN
Did you bring money?
Please take this and this.
I'll have a seat.
Here.
Why did you bring me
something I can't even eat?
Don't be picky with the buns.
Eat whatever you grab.
There's a certain flavor I like.
I like these filled with sweet red beans…
GIRIN STEAMED BUNS
…and this must be it.
Sweet red beans.
Good grief.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
You have the same appetite as your father.
What's wrong?
Did you think I'd run off
with your office deed?
Well…
I'm sorry for everything, sir.
Money wasn't something petty.
It was something so precious
that it could even make you feel
very petty.
On that day,
I was afraid I wouldn't be able
to do something that awful
if I saw your dad's face.
But at times, the CEO of a company
must take action to prove to his staff
that their CEO is willing
to do anything and everything
to protect them.
-Anything and everything.
-Except for crimes.
-Of course not. No crimes.
-Of course not.
All right, then.
-Thanks.
-Don't mention it, sir.
Thank you for the bun.
Don't finish everything.
Leave some for me.
There's a lot in here.
I didn't buy that many.
Containers swarm to Pusan Port for export,
but import containers are at a standstill,
displaying a polarization
in recent research.
On 15th of last month, Pusan Maritime
Affairs and Fisheries announced
the total export volume at Pusan Port
at the end of November
went up by 12.8%
compared to the previous month,
recording two digits
in the rate of increase.
However, the total import volume dropped
by 2.2%, displaying a great contrast.
I was listening.
You shouldn't listen to the radio
during working hours.
So, how much money do we have left?
About 7,000,000 won.
But it'll be gone by next month.
We have to pay rent too.
How's it working out?
I should've demanded four times more.
What is this?
Our New Year's cards look too messy.
Christmas seals are the holiday spirit.
TO MR. CHOI JUNG-HO
-Is that your handwriting?
-Don't you recognize it?
FROM TYPHOON TRADING
"It's the new year,
the Year of the Tiger."
"I wish you luck like a typhoon
to come your way in this coming year."
It's weird.
How would you put it?
"Happy New Year.
Sincerely, Typhoon Trading."
You're way too cold-hearted.
I'm going to the post office tomorrow,
so I'll send these then.
Okay. But you know,
I want to visit this place in person.
Hongshin Company?
It's in Pusan.
Yes, Pusan,
where dollars and exports flock in.
TICKETS ON WEEKDAYS CAN BE PURCHASED
ANYTIME VIA THE TRAIN CONDUCTOR
Gosh, it's my first time
coming to Pusan in ten years.
It's my first time.
Anyway, were you really invited?
Wasn't it just courtesy?
Yes, I was told to make sure I visit.
It was said out of courtesy!
-Gosh, what if we're a nuisance?
-We are?
It's just something people say.
-Come on.
-Mr. Kang Tae-poong?
Mr. Kang Tae-poong? Is that you?
It's you, right?
I recognized you right away!
Hey, you look just like your dad!
You look exactly the same,
with your fair complexion and long neck.
-What a good-looking man.
-Thank you.
I'm Jung Cha-ran of Hongshin Company.
I always ask people to visit,
but you're the first who actually came.
People of Pusan take promises seriously.
So did you dress up a bit
-to travel all the way to Pusan?
-Of course.
This isn't Pusan style.
What is this muffler?
-Lose it. It's too hot.
-I feel cold.
No, it's way too warm.
Your youth will keep you hot.
-Right?
-It's really cold.
Anyway…
Who are you?
Hello, my name is Oh Mi-seon.
JINWON TRADING
CURTAINS, HANSEOP BAGS
There are lots of things
to export from Pusan.
Take a good look.
My gosh.
I love the energy here.
Pusan is known for its energy,
and when it comes to energy,
you think of Pusan.
What's the most popular
in Pusan right now?
The most popular thing in Pusan?
Me.
Oh, my. I'm the most popular in Seoul!
-Are you that guy?
-Yes.
That means
Kang Tae-poong rules Seoul,
while Cha-ran owns Pusan.
-Well, just Apgujeong.
-Apgujeong?
-Yes.
-Hello, Ms. Jung.
-Hello.
Hey, there.
This glass noodle dish
is Pusan's delicacy.
-You have to try it.
-Can we export glass noodles?
-Glass noodles?
-Yes.
I want to try making
glass noodles that are flat and wider.
-Flat and wide?
-Yes.
I've never had it flat and wide.
-Would it taste good?
-I think it'll have a nice texture.
Please be careful.
Are you sending that to Shanghai?
It's the second floor here.
This is fun.
This is amazing.
I'll count these.
INTERNATIONAL WIRE TRANSFER
MONEY EXCHANGE
This is exactly why
I could never
cut off the men of the Kang family.
They may not be the most eloquent,
but they're modest in their actions.
Isn't that cute?
My gosh.
Look at the money.
Tae-poong.
-Yes?
-So?
Tell me what you want to do
and what you want to eat.
Well, it's not about what I want to eat.
I hear there are lots of dollars here.
-Dollars?
-Yes.
My goodness.
This Gukje Market is a place
that survived the Korean War
and the wreck of the aftermath.
You'll find any currency here
and everything you're looking for.
The real question is
who will get to them first.
I see.
-Let's go, Ms. Jung.
-I'm glad we came.
-It's already time?
-Yes, ma'am.
I have to exchange some money.
Think about what you want to do.
Excuse me. If you don't mind,
may I come along?
I'm just curious.
-Let's go.
-I will also take a tour outside.
All right. Sure. Let's all leave.
Goodness. The business is booming.
Stop it.
Have you ever seen Danish currency?
I've never seen this before.
Have you ever seen me turn down money?
I'll even take currencies from the Moon.
-Is that so?
-Goodbye.
-Have a good one.
Hey, wait. Just wait.
All right.
Okay, thank you.
This one. Please.
I wonder if Tae-poong
is getting around all right.
He probably is.
That was a rough one.
UJEONG SEAWEED
SAMIL VINYL
What the heck are you doing?
Will you be careful? You'll hurt yourself!
-You'll break everything.
-You okay?
I'm fine.
Goodness gracious.
-Coming through.
-Hurry up.
Hey, grab this one first.
-Where is it?
-This was for you.
-Be careful!
-You don't have to mind me.
Don't fall over and lose it
like you did last time!
-Hold it tightly!
-All right!
-Coming through!
-It's crowded here.
Make way, please.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Coming through. Please move.
-You're here.
-Hey, there.
How's business? Sold anything?
Just one.
All right. Look.
Crunch the numbers right
for three countries.
How much is the yen today?
It was 1,150 won
without the decimal points.
Okay.
Yuans are 181 won.
What's with this?
Is it out of batteries?
Cha-ran is getting old too.
It's been over a decade
since Cha-ran got old.
It's 2,436,910 won.
Wicked.
Is that right?
You're not too bad.
Pay him out. Have a good one.
-Okay. Bye.
-Goodbye.
Bye.
HYEONDAE TRADING
MYEONGSEONG TRADING
THE FUTURE OF MANAGEMENT
-Are you interested?
-Sorry?
Wait.
I'm Park Yun-cheol, the CEO of Shoe Park.
Read it backwards,
and it goes, Park's Shoe.
SHOE PARK
CEO PARK YUN-CHEOL
-You've done this for 30 years?
-Well, to be exact, it's been 32 years.
I took over the business
my father had started.
I am
just like you, Mr. CEO.
I find it uncomfortable
when people address me as the CEO.
I'm not a businessman.
I'm a researcher.
"CEO Kang Tae-poong"?
-Are these safety shoes?
-Yes, that's right.
If you're interested,
would you like to see some samples?
Look at this.
Did you see that?
It goes through with one strike.
Now, let's continue.
Stainless steel is a bit thicker
than that pot, isn't it?
But even this only takes a few strikes.
-Like this.
-Oh, my gosh.
See? Everything gets penetrated.
-All right.
-My gosh.
Don't be alarmed.
This frying pan is next.
What do you think will happen?
-I don't think it'll go through.
-You doubt it'll get penetrated?
No.
Get through!
Take a look.
Here's a regular safety shoe
out in the market.
See? It rips through.
And now, look at this.
Shoe Park's Safe.
Allow me to show you Shoe Park's product.
I'll slam it down as hard as I can.
Like this.
See? It's unscathed.
Check for yourself.
It's fine.
These aren't just shoes. It's science.
Yes, it took about three years to develop.
People can use these out on the field.
These will be useful.
-These will save people from tetanus.
-Yes.
Yes, you're right about that.
In simple terms,
these are the most comfortable
and safest safety shoes in the world.
Shoe Park's Safe.
What is it?
Why?
Hey!
Goodness gracious.
-You're a reckless young man.
-How much are these?
I'm not a man after money.
Have you ever exported these?
May safety prevail
all over the world for people's good.
Shoe Park's Safe.
Since you already have it on,
let me demonstrate one more thing for you.
Please don't worry.
Don't be scared.
-What? Me?
-Here we go.
-On me?
-Yes.
Here's Shoe Park's Safe.
How do you feel?
You feel fine, don't you?
Does it feel hot?
Not at all!
My gosh.
Our factory is right around here.
Would you like a tour?
Yes.
-All right.
-Let's go.
It doesn't feel hot, right?
I'm afraid it'll get hot soon.
You don't think so?
Come on in.
These are our finished products.
We keep them packaged
by different sizes, just like this.
These shoes are on amusement park rides.
Mr. Park, you may not be greedy,
but you're ambitious.
How many of these are there?
There aren't too many.
About 7,000 pairs, so 14,000 shoes.
You have 14,000 shoes?
Take a look at how these are made.
This way, please.
Come with me.
This is the area
where the shoes are made and built.
Take your time to look around.
Keep up the good work.
Let me show you something rad.
Take a look. This is…
Everything gets glued together,
and then it gets pressed together.
-It's the four-way compression.
-Four-way compression.
Isn't that rad?
Goodness gracious.
I told you not to do this.
This is how tacky my staff are.
THE BEST QUALITY!
Goodness gracious.
Don't do this from now on.
You're embarrassing me.
Take a look at this.
Look here. Right here.
Everything is done by hand.
It's a tough line of work,
so young people don't want to get in.
Up until about a decade ago,
people in Pusan made a living
by doing something like this.
But then
China began to bombard us
with unbelievably cheap labor.
Factories that worked
as subcontractors for brands
all had to shut down in the end.
The domestic market isn't much.
But I wanted
to go all-in on this business
and try my luck.
I don't care much for money,
but I do have
that relentless spirit in me.
Why isn't Tae-poong here yet?
Has that grown man gotten lost?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Oh!
Ms. Oh! You have to see this.
Hey, you.
-Guess what I got.
-What?
Pusan's famous fish cake?
What's this?
We're going to export this.
His eyes are googly and gone.
What's the big deal? What is it?
PURCHASE AGREEMENT
-What is this place?
-Why?
Here. Take this and cancel the agreement.
No, I can't do that.
I got these at a dirt-cheap price
for paying up front--
Kang Tae-poong!
Mr. Kang.
Nam-mo!
-Hey, Mom. What's up?
-Hey.
Two draft beers and one fried chicken.
Why are you asking me for beer?
The machine is out there.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Pull yourself together!
All right. I'm sorry. Oh, no.
My gosh!
My goodness!
What's wrong? That's hot!
What's wrong, Nam-mo?
No, I'm fine.
-Were you burnt?
-Table three.
You got burnt. Put ice on it
-or cold water.
-Okay.
It's for table three.
Goodness. It must hurt.
Gosh, what a mess.
-Please enjoy.
-Excuse me.
-We ordered first.
-Yes, you're right!
I'm sorry. That tabled ordered first.
Yes, I'm sorry.
-Please enjoy.
-Thanks.
Thank you for participating
in the New Star Competition.
Number 32, Wang Nam-mo,
you did not make the finals.
Welcome to Momo's Pub. A table for two?
-This way, please.
-Hello.
Please have a seat.
-Where are the adhesive bandages?
-For your hand? It's down there.
Under the sheet music. Yes.
-Where are you going, Mom?
-I have an appointment.
I'll make it quick.
But it's store hours.
It's something good.
Let me off just for today.
-You're really leaving like that?
-Thanks!
What's this?
DENTORICH PLUS TOOTHPASTE
Toothpaste?
Have a drink.
Thank you.
You might as well
throw it at me from there.
Leave if you don't want it.
Take a look, Ms. Oh.
This is the sole for the safety shoes.
It's called an outsole,
and it's very sturdy and strong.
Well… One moment.
Take a look.
What was that sound?
Hey.
I think you have customers.
Go see them.
Did you see that?
I mean,
the factory cost
for these shoes are 30,000 won,
but we're getting 500 pairs
for five million won.
It's only 10,000 won per pair.
Even at factory price,
we'll still earn threefold.
And fivefold if we sell it at 50,000 won.
We'll definitely make money.
Why are these so cheap?
Did you really see the products?
Yes, of course.
I saw a huge pile of shoes
in the warehouse.
The Grade Department Store here in Pusan
ordered 7,000 pairs
for their construction,
but they went bankrupt,
so they left the stock there.
Yes, that damned department store
has put an end to many businesses here.
But still, you can't just go
and sign the contract right away.
She's right. Why did you sign it so soon?
-Have you gone crazy?
-That's how I got these cheap.
I would lose my chance
if I took time to think.
This guy has some guts.
A guy need guts like these
to run a business.
The thing is,
the money he used isn't ours.
We have to make payments, so why did you…
Yes, that was way over the line!
Yes, exactly.
I wanted to get started,
sell something, and make a profit.
All right, man.
I don't know what's going on,
but if it already happened,
don't try to patch it up.
But you know,
just do your best to be a success.
-Yes, that's right.
-I know.
Yes, you're right.
Have a drink and make amends.
I'd like a cola, please.
What's he saying? Hey!
I need a spoon to pick my ears.
I literally get drunk
even after one glass of soju.
Stop talking nonsense.
Hey, I ran over at once
because you asked me to come.
How dare you not accept a drink, you punk?
Have a drink. You can't say no.
This can be dangerous.
I'll cover for him.
Ms. Oh Mi-seon.
You must be quite a drinker.
Well, I know how to keep up at a party.
That sounds awesome.
But you know,
it's not a lot of fun if it's just us two.
Do you remember those boys?
I know one of them.
He said you were pretty.
-He only had his eyes on you.
-Really?
Wait. Just one moment.
Are you here to hang out?
What's so solid about those guys,
and how is she pretty?
Good grief.
He's making sure this is his turf.
All right, kiddo.
Hey, about Shoe Park.
I know everything
that goes on around here.
Why does it sound so unfamiliar?
It sounds new to me.
Tae-poong.
Hey, what's wrong with him?
My goodness.
He really can't handle alcohol?
Let's just enjoy ourselves.
You surprised me.
Why? What's wrong?
-One second.
-What is it?
Here.
Look here, Ms. Oh.
I WON'T MAKE YOU MAD
Look.
What I want to say to you
is written right here.
I won't…
From now on,
-I won't make you mad.
-Jeez.
I promise I won't make you mad, Ms. Oh.
I WON'T
It says "I won't."
I won't do it again.
Are you going to do this every time?
Then let me tell you my wish.
Or should I save it?
What do you mean?
I drank on your behalf back there.
You didn't drink for me!
-You told me not to drink.
-Whatever.
Just do those things only with me.
I have to write down my wish.
-Do you have paper?
-No.
Give me your hand.
Come on, give it to me.
All right.
My
wish
coupon.
I'm saving it.
I'll make sure I use this someday.
Got it?
I think
we should walk a little now.
Jeez.
Careful.
Do you feel confident?
I'll have to try.
Those 500 pairs of 10,000-won shoes?
-I'm sure I can sell those.
-No, not that.
Can you be a real CEO…
for our business?
Let's see…
I don't think
I know what it means to be a CEO yet.
But I will
do anything and everything
for the company.
I know I feel confident
to be a trader.
Ms. Oh, you are…
like a cosmos.
-It's cold.
-Jeez.
My gosh.
My feet are all wet.
That's not a big deal.
-Your feet are barely wet.
-No, they're drenched.
-Come on.
-Where are you going?
-Stop it!
-Those are the good days.
They looked miserable earlier,
but they're running like puppies now.
That's why they're still in their youth.
Get back here.
I know I can sell all those shoes!
Come back here! Come!
Step back, will you?
SALVATION ARMY DONATION KETTLE
It's so weird.
I don't go to church,
but I feel great during Christmas season.
Carols sound merry…
-Hello.
-…and the cakes taste delicious too.
I even feel like doing a good deed
every now and then.
Have a good one.
It feels like I'll see a present
next to me when I wake up.
How can I put this?
It feels like a miracle will happen.
NOTICE OF EVICTION
Why is the door open?
Mom?
-Tae-poong.
-Mom?
-Are you Mr. Kang Tae-poong?
-Yes.
Have you received the mail?
What mail?
I'm sorry.
REMINDER - OVERDUE
Your apartment unit
has been auctioned off.
We will now confiscate
your tangible properties.
You may take necessities
to sustain your life.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
We're behind at work too.
This is the house.
-Come quickly. Grab what you can.
-Goodness!
-Let's hurry.
-My gosh.
-Mom.
-Move!
-You need to stop!
-I don't care.
-This is obstruction of official duties!
-Darn it!
What do you think you're all doing?
-Take this.
-Stop it. Mister!
What's with you?
-Pack your stuff.
-What?
Sir, don't do this.
Ma'am! Come on.
I already know there is no Santa Claus.
Let me get it.
One second.
Wait.
My goodness.
Tae-poong, have we been
thrown out into the streets?
Are you okay, Mom?
Why didn't you put on something warmer?
They didn't let me take anything
that was worth money.
-What time is it?
-What?
-Why? What is it?
-Stay here for a moment.
-Where are you going?
-Stay there.
Wait, where are you going?
No, not the back gates.
-I'll be right back.
-Don't run.
Mom.
-This could've turned out really bad.
-Why?
I think I was really clever
when I said I'd pick this up later.
This was your dad's last present.
-Button up.
-Okay.
-Let's go before anyone sees us.
-Let's go.
-I'll take both.
-No.
-I'll take these.
-Let me have one.
-I got these.
-Goodness.
-Let's go.
-My gosh.
Yes. Bye.
Okay, take care.
Bye.
How can people be so cold?
I can't believe
no one is willing to take us in.
Tae-poong, where do we go from here?
-Mom.
-Yes?
Let's go and stay…
with Dad tonight.
What are you talking about?
We have to stay strong
and think about a way to rise above this!
How can you say
something like that to your mother?
What's wrong with you?!
You're awful!
I already feel cold and hungry.
Why are you adding to this?
What is wrong with you?
TYPHOON TRADING
This is where Dad is.
YEOPJIP RAMYEON
It's cooked perfectly right now.
All right.
Enjoy your food.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
You're really good at making cup ramyeon.
I make even better coffee
in a 3-2-2 combo.
I'll make you a cup after this.
You really sound like an office worker.
I'm so glad I raised you into a man
who can do just about anything.
You know what?
Do you think I took after you?
Of course.
Your features and skin complexion
all resemble me.
-You think so?
-Anyway, this is odd.
I had zero appetite earlier,
but this is so easy to eat.
Why is this so good?
-It's warm, isn't it?
-Yes, it's good.
But without a day like Christmas,
this winter would be too long.
It'd be too cold.
There's a draft in this office.
Are you cold?
You'll get facial paralysis
if you sleep in the cold.
-Have you watched Tears of the Dragon?
-Of course, I have.
Tae-poong.
Everything feels like a nightmare to me.
It'll be so nice if I wake up
back at our place
after a good night's sleep.
Goodness.
Well, as long as we're together,
that's where our home is.
Look.
Oh, my.
I bought this with my hard-earned money.
Isn't it pretty?
It is.
This is kind of embarrassing,
but before,
when I saw people who did
hard labor out in the street,
I used to feel bad for them.
So I always thought
I was a really kind-hearted guy.
You are kind-hearted.
I realized people who sweat and work hard
weren't pitiful nor great.
That's just how you make money.
So, Dad,
Merry Christmas.
Time to go to bed.
So?
-Are you keeping an eye on Kang Tae-poong?
-Yes, sir.
I confirmed that
he moved out of his house.
Is that so?
CONTRACTOR: PYO MERCHANT MARINE
I wonder what it feels like
to lose everything one after another
at such a young age.
THE WIND CANNOT STOP ME
TYPHOON FAMILY
Hello.
My name is Oh Beom,
number 47 in first grade.
-Cue!
-All right. Cue!
I already showed it to over ten places,
and some of them showed interest.
Are you nervous? I'm not nervous at all.
All done.
I'm so sorry.
Did you borrow money from thugs?
What about my money? Where's my money?
That money is the only reason
I'm still alive.
-Is this fun to you?
-Yes. It's a lot of fun.
Don't try too hard.
You can lean on me
when things become too tough.
-The products are coming from Pusan?
-Hello.
I need to take interest.
I suppose you're scared now.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn